const quizQuestion = [
  {
    question: " '#' Commonly known as a hashtag, its technical name is?",
    number: "1",
    choice: {
      a: "Pound",
      b: "Octothorpe",
      c: "Apostrophe",
    },
    answer: "Octothorpe",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the national animal of Scotland?",
    number: "2",
    choice: {
      a: "Narwhal",
      b: "Loch Ness Monster",
      c: "Unicorn",
    },
    answer: "Unicorn",
  },
  {
    question: "What does M&M stand for?",
    number: "3",
    choice: {
      a: "Maintenance and Management",
      b: "Eminem",
      c: "Mars and Murrie",
    },
    answer: "Mars and Murrie",
  },
  {
    question: "What was the first soft drink to ever be in space?",
    number: "4",
    choice: {
      a: "Coca-Cola",
      b: "Pepsi",
      c: "Baha Blast",
    },
    answer: "Coca-Cola",
  },
  {
    question: "How much does it cost to make a $1 bill?",
    number: "5",
    choice: {
      a: "50 cents",
      b: "25 cents",
      c: "5 cents",
    },
    answer: "5 cents",
  },
  {
    question: "What was the first toy to be advertised on T.V.?",
    number: "6",
    choice: {
      a: "Lincoln Logs",
      b: "Mr. Potato Head",
      c: "Dreidel",
    },
    answer: "Mr. Potato Head",
  },
  {
    question: "Which country has the oldest continually used national flag?",
    number: "7",
    choice: {
      a: "Denmark",
      b: "France",
      c: "Brazil",
    },
    answer: "Denmark",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the loudest animal in the Earth?",
    number: "8",
    choice: {
      a: "Fish",
      b: "Elephant",
      c: "Sperm Whale",
    },
    answer: "Sperm Whale",
  },
  {
    question: "Which planet in our solar system does not have any moons?",
    number: "9",
    choice: {
      a: "Mercury",
      b: "Earth",
      c: "Saturn",
    },
    answer: "Mercury",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the most common birthday in the United States",
    number: "10",
    choice: {
      a: "August 8th",
      b: "July 23rd",
      c: "September 9th",
    },
    answer: "September 9th",
  },
];

export {quizQuestion};